mactrast.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy

This is mactrast.com and the following privacy policy statement serves as a disclaimer to notify users of the website practices and its data use.

Please reach out to contact@mactrast.com for questions that are not addressed in the below privacy policy statement.

The privacy of our readers is of extreme importance to us. We will never share or sell your personally identifiable information such as email address, phone number, or home address.

We use third party analytics and advertising apps that place cookies on your personal computer. These cookies store information about our visitors preferences, and record how our visitors interact with mactrast.com

## Content quality

While is strive for the most accurate reporting possible, we cannot offer our users and or visitors guaranteed accuracies. Stories that are not considered news will be filed under our “rumor” section.  Whenever possible we will make an attempt to adjust or amend information deemed inaccurate provided on our site that we have control over (E.G. editorial content). Usage of this website is offered without any guarantees. If a visitor has a complaint about content or anything else contained within Mactrast, please email us.

For each visitor to this website, our web server automatically attempts to recognize the consumer’s domain name or IP address and/or e-mail address (where possible or when specified by the user, in comments or otherwise).

## Information we collect

We may collect an IP address and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our website, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our comments, forums, bulletin board, or any other means, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of users who subscribe to our email newsletter, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. Any and all comments submitted to the website may be filtered, edited, or modified as deemed necessary to be appropriate for the service. Discussion is encouraged, but any inflammatory, offensive, inappropriate, promotional, or nonsensical comments may be removed or modified as necessary and as deemed appropriate. We do not endorse hate speech and will take action to minimize exposure of such acts.

The information we collect is used for internal aggregation, and is used to improve the content of our website, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

With respect to use of cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences and to display Google Adsense Doubleclick DART information. Third party advertisers may use cookies as well, and some social sharing services may also use cookies, though these are beyond the scope of mactrast.com.

Mactrast offers opt-in mail list subscriptions with a digest of posts. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address or follow the unsubscribe link in our emails.

## Ad Servers

With respect to Mactrast’s ad servers: We try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our website. Mactrast earns commission on sales through these ads. As a result of your visit to our site and upon clicking on relevant ads, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557

http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

We may use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our website. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, consult:

http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or at contact@mactrast.com

## Affiliate link use on Mactrast

When appropriate, mactrast.com will include links to products or services with ‘affiliate’ codes attached to them, this gives mactrast.com commission on sales through those links. This commission goes to supporting the production and maintenance of the site.

Mactrast.com is a participant in the StackCommerce and Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com and StackSocial products. Purchases made through these links may offer commissions to MacTrast.com.

Whenever possible, we will specify any special endorsements, advertisements, or sponsorships. If you have any questions regarding this, email us: contact@mactrast.com
